This video is for you to introduce the function related to rendering
In the previous version of the Mac system only support CPU rendering
Now the new version also supports GPU rendering
This makes it even on Apple Silicon Mac
Vray rendering speed can be achieved faster
Let us use the test project file to check GPU rendering
First open the rendering window
Then click on the rendering property icon
After rendering settings appear
Open the download menu in the rendering tool category
As you can see, there is a GPU here
Now let us run the actual rendering
You will see the result in the rendering window
Just like CPU rendering
GPU rendering supports all materials provided by Kolo
And rendering speed is faster than before
This function is only used to install the latest version of updated SDK
If your SDK is not automatically updated
Please be sure to manually install the latest version
Now even on Mac
You can also install it
And you can experience the high-speed GPU rendering
In the new version
We can add different focal lengths for the customized view
Open the rendering window
And change the current view under the video property
To the customized view
Now we need to create a customized view
Open the synchronized rendering
To better set the customized view
To the final desired position
After setting the customized view of the user
Under the lens property
Open this actual camera
Only rendering
And open the depth of field
We will change the current view to the customized view
You can see the customized view added in the list below
We also need to click on the setting focus point
Now we only need to be in the rendering window under synchronization
Click on the mouse button in the position you want to focus on
You can see the changes in the view under the lens
In the property editor
Next we use the same operation
To set all the settings for the customized view
This new function can help us
Save a lot of time in rendering
And better control the depth of each customized view
From rendering
Satisfy the rendering image we are focusing on
From the 2025 version
We can use the background generated by AI
And the rendering image in the hole
To create a more high-quality rendering image
Easily
First of all
From the top of the menu
Click on rendering AI model workshop
In the window that appears
Click on the background option in the upper right corner
You can use the background function
Want to use the background function of AI model workshop
You first need to use the background conversion picture
Includes a transparent background image of virtual models and clothing
Please refer to the visual image displayed in the AI model workshop
We first need to change the background
We first render the original picture
Download the project file of the virtual model wearing the costume
Adjust the 3D window angle to the angle you want
Then click on the rendering in the top main menu
Open the rendering window
Start rendering the costume
To ensure that the original picture and the background picture generated or uploaded
Smooth and seamless integration
We provide recommended picture size and rendering guide
To check these suggestions
Click on the magic stick in the rendering tool column on the right side first
As you can see
Under the original picture part
You can see the visual image and recommended settings
First of all, it is recommended to set the rendering picture size
Between 2160 pixels to 4320 pixels
If the rendering picture size is more than 4320 pixels
It automatically adjusts the picture size to 4320 pixels or less
At the same time, it will maintain a fixed ratio
If the picture size is set to 2160 pixels
It can still be used
But in order to get a better picture size
And a more natural effect
It is best to use at least 2160 pixels of the picture
The focal point is less and the quality is clear
Secondly, the main body and background must be clear and variable
If due to light or shadow
Causing the original picture to be unable to correctly identify
The result may appear unnatural
Due to the quality of the original picture
Will directly affect the final result
Therefore, please pay attention to this when rendering
Click on the picture video attribute
Because it will eventually generate a square
With a background rendering picture
Therefore, when setting the rendering size of the original picture
Please pay attention
The pixel value of its picture size
Depends on the maximum value of the rendering size set in the original picture
If you set the original picture size to 2160 x 3840 pixels
The final output picture size will also be 3840 x 3840 pixels
According to the suggestion, after adjusting the settings
Click on the final rendering to output high quality images
Click on the AI model workshop again
You can see that the final rendering picture has been automatically uploaded
By switching between the window of the AI model workshop and the window of the rendering window
You can immediately merge the background picture into the rendering picture
Check the results and adjust accordingly
Achieve the final effect we want
Under the background selection of the AI model workshop
You can choose two ways
Proposal or picture
For the proposal
You can enter the description text you need
Or select the keyword to generate a picture
For the picture
You can upload the picture file you like
And use it as a background
Let's take a look at the operation method of the prompt
You can enter the text you need to describe the background
You can also click on the first icon in the lower right corner of the box
Keyword suggestion
Choose the word you need from the recommended keywords
When you choose the keyword you need here
They will be added to the text prompt section
For example, select the city street and industrial style
You will see that these keywords will automatically be added to the prompt section
If you want to remove the selected keywords
You can click on the X button on the right side of the prompt section
Or in the keyword suggestion
Click on the selected keyword again
You can cancel the selection of the keyword
After entering the prompt or selecting the keyword
Click on the start generation next to it
You can generate a background picture
Press the reset button at the bottom of the background picture
It will restore the generated background picture to default
By clicking on the result displayed after the start generation
You can see that even if you use the same prompt
The function of AI model workshop to generate a background
A new picture will be generated every time
But if you want to keep the existing picture
Change the picture on the basis
You can click on the icon with the second big needle shape
Keep the key word input
Then change the prompt position
If the prompt is not changed
Or add a new prompt
Start generating a new background picture
For example, click on the key word to keep the input
And add the text prompt bright
To make the background picture look brighter
Then click on start generation
You can see that the newly generated background picture has been adjusted to be brighter
At the same time, the original composition is still maintained
Finally, when you want to get creative inspiration from random background pictures
You can use the random generation function
Which is the third dice icon
This function will automatically generate random background description text
Help you quickly create creative
If you want to write a prompt
You can click on the pencil icon in the upper right corner of the key word prompt box
It can clear the prompt to make it easier for us to rewrite the prompt
Or use the key word function to keep the input
To make more detailed changes
In addition, click on the question mark icon on the right side
You can visit the AI model workshop's handbook
Click on history record
Here you can see all the previously generated picture charts
You can also double click on the picture to re-upload the picture and its corresponding text prompt
You can choose your favorite picture from the history record
Then click on the save icon in the upper right corner
Save it as a PNG file
You can also select all the pictures and save all the images
If the picture is not saved separately
These picture history records will only be kept until the shell software is closed
Next, select the picture option
Then click on upload
Add the background picture we just created
However, please note that when uploading the picture
You must use a picture with copyright or no copyright issues
After successfully adding the picture file
Click on the bottom of the window to start creating
Apply it to the original picture
If you want to redo the original picture and background picture
Just click on the redo button next to the creation
It can be restored to default state
If you are satisfied with the result of the creation
You can click on the save at the bottom of the window
And choose to save the picture in a PNG or JPG format
Please note that the final picture will be saved as a square
The specific size depends on the original picture in the picture video attribute
The maximum pixel value of the set picture size
If you first use AI to create a face picture in the face selection
Find the hair of the created person
There are flaws in the hand
You can use the three optimization functions in the window of the output image
They are hair optimization, hand optimization, clothing optimization
Click on the hair optimization and hand optimization for this picture
You can see that the hair of the final created picture
The hands have been optimized
Improved the overall beauty
At this time, we are applying the background to this picture
When switching to the background option
The latest created face picture is the one we created
Will be automatically set to the original picture
To make your workflow more convenient
We will add the new created face picture to the background
And save it
By using the background generation function of the AI model workshop
You can easily create the clothes you designed
The various background effects that match the virtual model